Guide to the Food and food marketing collection, 1942-2015.
Food and food marketing collection,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Food and food marketing collection, 1942-2015.
6560
4.3 cubic ft.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection of catalogs and brochures from food producers and purveyors, kitchen equipment companies, and other direct mail marketers relating to food, lifestyle, and cooking.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection of catalogs and brochures from food producers and purveyors, kitchen equipment companies, and other direct mail marketers relating to food, lifestyle, and cooking.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Food -- Marketing.; Food -- Aesthetics.; Food consumption.; Cookware.; Kitchen utensils; Cooking.; Entertaining.; Lifestyles.; Wine -- Marketing.; Coffee brewing -- Equipment and supplies.; Coffee brewing -- Equipment and supplies; Cooking; Cookware; Entertaining; Food consumption; Food -- Marketing; Kitchen utensils; Lifestyles; Wine -- Marketing
Form and Genre Terms:
Catalogs
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Food Marketing Materials
CONTAINER LIST
- Food Marketing Materials
  - Allen Brothers Steaks, 2000-2003, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Armour & Company, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Art of Eating, Undated (Box 1)
  - Artful Home, 2007 (Box 1)
  - B (Beecher's, Bertie County Peanuts, Burgers' Smokehouse), 2007, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Bakers Catalog (King Arthur Flour), 2002, 2004, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Better Homes & Gardens, The Country Gentleman, and Ladies Home Journal (o/s), 1930-1948 (Box 1)
  - Bigelow Teas, Undated (Box 1)
  - Bissinger's, 2010 (Box 1)
  - C (Cascade Complete, Christmas Cookings from the Heart, Chukar Cherries, Clipper Magazine, Cookings Club), 2002, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Chef's - 2004 - Feb 2005, 2004-2005-02 (Box 1)
  - Chef's - April - Fall 2005, 2005-04-2005-09 (Box 1)
  - Chef's - Holiday 2005, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Chef's - Holiday 2008 - Fall 2010, 2008-2010-10 (Box 1)
  - Chef's - Holiday 2010, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Chef's Gifts, 2007 (Box 1)
  - Chefs Tool Catalog, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Cheryl & Co., 2009-2010 (Box 1)
  - Chico's, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Cook's Country (o/s), Undated (Box 1)
  - Cook's Illustrated, 2004-2005 (Box 1)
  - Cooking Enthusiast, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Cooking.com, 2003-12 (Box 1)
  - Crate & Barrel, 2001, 2005, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Creative Cook's Kitchen (recipes), Undated (Box 1)
  - Cryer Creek Kitchens (Collins St. Bakery), 2002 (Box 1)
  - Dean and Deluca, 2000-2003 (Box 1)
  - Dean and Deluca, 2005-2008 (Box 1)
  - Dinner tonight, Undated (Box 1)
  - Discrimination in restaurants: "Have You Heard What's Cooking?", Undated (Box 1)
  - Duck River Fish Farm, 2002 (Box 1)
  - E, 2010 (Box 2)
    Emeril's Red Marble Steaks
    Etoile
  - E.A.T., Undated (Box 2)
  - Earth & Vine Provisions, Undated (Box 2)
  - Eleni's, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Eli's Essentials, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Ethel M. Chocolates, 2000 (Box 2)
  - F, 2007, 2010 (Box 2)
    Fat Witch Bakery
    Fauchon s'Emporte
    Fratelli Carli
  - Fanny May, 2002 (Box 2)
  - French Cooking: "The French Cooks' Syndicate", 1945 (Box 2)
  - French Country Living, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Gevalia Coffee, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Godiva, 2000-2009 (Box 2)
  - Godiva, 2009-2010 (Box 2)
  - The Good Cook, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
  - Gourmet, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Gourmet Center, 2009 (Box 2)
  - Gourmet Marketplace, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Gracewood Grove, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Great American Home Baking, Undated (Box 2)
  - Green Mountain Coffee Roasters, 2004-2010 (Box 2)
  - Grill Lovers, 2005 (Box 2)
  - Gump's, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Hacienda Home, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Harry & David, 2000-2010 (Box 2)
  - Haute Home Cuisine, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Easy to Bake Easy to Make, Undated (Box 2)
  - Hickory Farms, 2009 (Box 2)
  - King Arthur Flour, 2008-2010 (Box 2)
  - Kitchen Cook, Undated (Box 2)
  - La Tienda, 2009-2010 (Box 2)
  - Lands' End, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Latte, Undated (Box 2)
  - Le Creuset, 2004-2005 (Box 2)
  - Legal Seafood, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Lenotre, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Mackenzie Ltd., 2003-2010 (Box 2)
  - Mackenzie-Childs, 2010-10-2010-11 (Box 2)
  - Marshall Fields, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Martha Stewart, 2000-2003 (Box 2)
  - Master Chef's, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Meduri, Fall 2004 (Box 3)
  - Silver, China, and Crystal, Undated (Box 3)
    Fostoria
    Syracuse China
    Michael C. Fina
  - Mrs. Fields, 2002, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Murray's, 2009-2011 (Box 3)
  - Napa Style, 2002-2005 (Box 3)
  - Napa Style, 2002-2003, 2007 (Box 3)
  - Napa Style, 2009-2010 (Box 3)
  - Nordstrom, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Norm Thompson, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Oregon's Bounty, 2008 (Box 3)
  - Olive & Cocoa, 2009-2010 (Box 3)
  - P, 2007 (Box 3)
    A Passion for Baking
    Phillips
  - Pecans Plain & Fancy, 2005-2011 (Box 3)
  - Penzays Spices, 2004-2010 (Box 3)
  - Petrossian Paris, Undated (Box 3)
  - Pfaelzer Brothers, 2003, 2009 (Box 3)
  - Pittman & Davis, 2002-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 3)
  - The Popcorn Factory, 2002 (Box 3)
  - PCD - Professional Cutlery Direct, 2000 (Box 3)
  - David Rosengarten's Recipes, Resources & Reviews (o/c), 2005 (Box 3)
  - Richart, Winter 2005 (Box 3)
  - River Street Sweets, 2009 (Box 3)
  - Room Service Home, 2007 (Box 3)
  - Savannah's Candy Kitchen, 2009 (Box 3)
  - Sciabica's, 2006-2007 (Box 3)
  - Scully & Scully, 2009 (Box 3)
  - Sea Bear Wild Salmon, 2010-11 (Box 3)
  - See's Candy, 2000-2005 (Box 3)
  - See's Candy, 2007-2010 (Box 3)
  - Sharon O'Connor's Menus and Music, 2011 (Box 4)
  - Sherry-lehmann.com, 2003-2008 (Box 4)
  - Smith & Hawken, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Smithfield Marketplace, 2009-2010 (Box 4)
  - Source Perrier Collection, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Stahmann's Estate Grown Pecans, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Starbucks, Fall 2009 (Box 4)
  - Stonewall Kitchen, 2001-2010 (Box 4)
  - Sur la Table, 2000-2003, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Sweets in Bloom, 2002 (Box 4)
  - A Taste of California, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - The Vermont Country Store, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Viansa, Fall 2002 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Diner, 2009-2010 (Box 4)
  - Viva Terra, 2007, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Wegmans, 2002, 2008-2010 (Box 4)
  - Whitman's Quality Foods, Undated (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2001, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2004-2005 (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2005, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2009-2010 (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Williams-Sonoma, 2010 (Box 4)
  - Wine, 2001, 2004-2005 (Box 4)
  - Wine & All That Jazz, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Wine and Cooking Clubs, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - Wine Country Gift Baskets, 2001, 2003, 2007, 2009-2010 (Box 4)
  - The Wine Enthusiast, 2000-2004, 2007, 2009-2010 (Box 4)
  - The Wisconsin Cheeseman, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Wolferman's, 2002-2005, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Zabar's, 2001-2002, 2004-2011 (Box 4)
  - Zagat Survey, 2007 (Box 4)
  - Zingerman's, 2003-2005, 2007, 2009-2010 (Box 4)
  - Assorted Cooking and Kitchen Catalogs, 2008-2011 (Box 5)
    Wegmans
    Mackenzie
    Godiva
    Williams-Sonoma
    Crate & Barrel
    Chefs
    King Arthur Flour
    Meduri
    Stonewall Kitchen
  - Assorted Cooking and Kitchen Catalogs, 2014-2016 (Box 6)
    Lucky Peach
    See's Candies